https://animesuperhero.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy sets out how animesuperhero.com uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website. animesuperhero.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. If we should ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you may be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES
animesuperhero.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically as your continued use of the site constitutes acceptance of any changes to the Terms of Service, Privacy Policy and General Rules of Conduct. We may periodically require you to reconfirm agreement to Terms of Service, Privacy Policy and General Rules of Conduct.  This policy is effective from 5/17/2018.
WHAT WE COLLECT
animesuperhero.com collects information about users supplied during account registration and during participation in certain activities on our website, including giveaways. This includes IP address, name, location, physical address, e-mail address, age and gender. We also store your provided personal preferences related to animesuperhero.com in your account data.
Your physical location, gender, date of membership and last login date is used in your animesuperhero.com User Profile to foster a better sense of community at our site. In addition you have the option of displaying your birthdate. If you wish to hide this data, you may do so in your Account Profile page.
When users request pages from our server, our Web server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. These addresses are used by computers on the network to send the requested pages to users.animesuperhero.comdoes not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission.
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER
animesuperhero.com uses users’ IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We primarily use IP addresses to track fraudulent user activity (including but not limited to: the use of multiple accounts, account sharing, illegal forum activity.)
Your browser type and version are also detected to better enhance your user experience and improve our products and services.
We may combine demographic information supplied by a user at registration with site usage data to provide profiles, in aggregate form, about our users and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. We may share this composite information with our advertisers to help them better understand our services.
We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.
animesuperhero.com will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
We may provide your personal information to law enforcement if you have actively engaged harassment of another user, threatened them with physical abuse, mental abuse or violence or if we are required to by law.
HOW WE USE COOKIES
animesuperhero.com uses cookies to deliver content specific to users’ interests and to keep a record of their preferences. This information is used to assist us in creating a site that will serve the needs of our users.
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You may choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
ADVERTISING
animesuperhero.com may use user supplied information in combination with site usage information to help display advertisements relevant to the users interest and navigation patterns. animesuperhero.com may use cookies to help in tracking these patterns but does not store or collect a personal data in combination with user supplied information.
animesuperhero.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address, telephone number or other specifically sensitive information) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to your site. animesuperhero.com’s visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using animesuperhero.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of animesuperhero.com’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
These third-party vendors also may collect information directly from your device, such as your IP address, information about your browser or operating system; may combine our personal and non-personal information about you with information from other sources; and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. To opt-out of third party cookies, please go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices. To opt-out of the use of your mobile device ID for targeted advertising, please see http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices.
DISCLOSURE REGARDING GOOGLE DISPLAY ADVERTISING
We have implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). Visitors can opt-out (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings.
animesuperhero.com, along with third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to the site.
animesuperhero.com uses the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting feature to identify trends in the usage of its website which may be published in reports for internal use.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
animesuperhero.com may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, animesuperhero.com does not have any control over that other website. Therefore, animesuperhero.com cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
SECURITY
animesuperhero.com is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us through this form (https://animesuperhero.com/contactus/).
If you have an account with animesuperhero.com, you may edit your details at any time via this form. (https://animesuperhero.com/forums/account/)
If you no longer wish to use your animesuperhero.com account, you may request all Personally Identifiable Information in your account be anonymized at any time by writing to or emailing us through this form (http://animesuperhero.com/contactus/).
If you are subscribed to our updates via feedburner, you may unsubscribe at feedburner’s website (http://feeds.feedburner.com/toonzone).
Users who wish to use animesuperhero.com must agree to the terms detailed above. Continued use of animesuperhero.com constitutes acceptance of the Terms of Service, Privacy Policy and General Rules of Conduct.
Contents
PRIVACY POLICY CHANGESWHAT WE COLLECTWHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHERHOW WE USE COOKIESADVERTISINGDISCLOSURE REGARDING GOOGLE DISPLAY ADVERTISINGLINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESSECURITYCONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Search Anime Superhero
Comic Book SolicitationsAnime Superhero Forums
Featured Posts Anime RPG & MUD
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
©
